and it's analyze this if you want did
you know that scientifically all the
stuff coming out of your exhaust box
should be exploitable yeah but it's not
because of a catalytic converter no you
you you the ones without a cat catalytic
and everything else never exploded when
it come out the exhaust either cuz what
they don't teach you is that when you
fire these things in the engine it swaps
a charge and that charge is on those
things and those things they don't tell
you it's only one charge on those gases
out your exhaust what will make them
fire make them go Bank okay but when
they burnt and come through your engine
it's on the opposite
charge it's the gas is what they say
that they can make burn but they can't
make them burn once they come through
your engine my uncle okay um he he had a
completely sealed engine and what he was
doing is when it when the exhaust stuff
come out when your exhaust gases come
out he had a stainless plate he put a
certain frequency onto the stainless
plate drove the Flaming gases over
changed the charges on them put them
straight back into the engine and the
the car would run completely so you know
you get to one speed no more nothing
else is added and you just cruise at
that speed forever you just change what
goes in comes out changes the charge
every time it comes back out goes back
in and those gases explode okay so you
want to you want to speed up he just
added a little tiny bit of extra and you
got to a high speed you want to drop
ribs you're little little bit out got s
don't take it right back around so you
had a valve to L in and out and he was
able to run off those but they got these
motors now what is 7200 hours they got
these gases in cylinders they've had
these motors and everything else running
and they just take the gas out of there
pump it through the engine there's no
out no intake and no exhaust and take it
over and it goes into cylinder when it's
gone over into cylinder there it's lost
its charge so they
recharge and then they can do another
7200 hours and then when it's dead flat
over here they recharge and but I won't
tell you about that either cuz I don't
want you to know that your gases have
opposite charges but science teaches
every action is an opposite equal
reaction so what's the opposite of
fire not
fire what's the opposite of north south
is
so I put this down right you got to get
this science teaches for every action
there is an opposite e reaction yeah
okay this is about your magnets
too so that is
North okay so finger watching North
what's the opposite of North opposite
equal yeah I'll drop this one for a
second so that's sth what's the opposite
of
itself
now what else is it so he can't
stop can't stop can't stop there's no
stopping any damn
thing so what does a magnet
do okay so the opposite of North is
South the opposite of South is North the
opposite
of you know it's South north north south
you you're star me you're finished no
you're not now you say oh East and West
no because that's not an opposite equal
that's a
90° up down no that's
90° opposite equal so really when you
ask what's the opposite forget about the
magnets and the fingers the the question
comes down to it what have you asked the
question you asked is what is the
opposite
equal so now change all that forget all
those components and fingers and magnets
and Fields what you were aiming and go
to the question and the question was
opposite
equal so what is the opposite of
H
fingers magnet do B magnet the opposite
of opposite is
get the fingers
on
Bingo equilibrium there is no North
there is no South there's no there's no
East West no up down y there's none of
those y you have put together your north
and south and they're both equal and not
opposites one is that way one's that one
fights is one you want to really know it
they're not opposite equals because
North negative North negative is always
stronger than South positive doesn't
matter in all electrical frequency feels
doesn't matter okay so we'll just call
it Opposite so you bring them back in
and you make an equilibrium when you
make an equilibrium that's what I've
done on those things that you did there
when I made an equilibrium you don't
have a north and a South which means
that you don't have a push or a pull so
one way is Magnus pull the other way
is they won't come together so I change
that and I equalize them and the flamers
don't do anything but you know while
they're not doing anything they're
thousands of times more stronger than
each single
pole you know two of together is a
thousand times more stronger than a
single so if you knew how to get that
power off from there you got yourself no
resistance no North no South no pull no
push you got yourself free of Freedom
you understand
and that freedom will outut and guess
what it don't need to do doesn't need to
rotate doesn't need to go through North
South north
south it just sits there and gives
out it doesn't
rotate doesn't need to because give me
the why do would it have to rotate to go
through any field when no other field
interferes with it because all the
fields are there equal at the same time
so in essence then you could keep those
magnets down in a neutral position yeah
and make use of the fuel pres service
that they create and then extracts power
out of it definitely that's how some
people have said they can get so many
volts so a foot off the ground they can
get so more volts foot off more foot off
the ground more more more okay yeah and
you have same
plates and they say well you need
opposites you need a different metal so
the first batteries used to be opposite
Metals okay okay and then they found out
and they don't like telling you they're
using lead and Lead oxide now okay so
and that isn't one lead plate clean on
both sides and all around and one dirty
plate oxidized all
around that splits itself so you get
clean dirty clean dirty and what happens
is it Stacks a different way and what
happens is the only charge that you get
out of the battery and everything El is
between there and there none on the ends
none on the other sides none on the tops
bottoms or anything but if you want to
look a positive or negative charg in
liquids did you know they 0° angle your
oxygen all comes off the face plate from
top to bottom no
hard comes at the K so you put it there
and everything else that's all going
that way that's all going that way
that's 90° what'll be nice if you just
turn them
around and line them up to there and
there there' be no
electrolyte there be no no
resistance okay it is superc conduct
with nothing in between and then if that
one there is going up and down you turn
them and drive them up and down as well
so you finish up the negative
resistance negative is a opposite of a
positive you would end up with neutral
zero NE side so you got to save
right you got save you don't end up with
it
okay because in the battery you have
current which takes place between the
plates and you have electron current
which only flows on the outside of the
circuit the electron C doesn't fly
through the battery and the iron Curr
doesn't fly outside the battery and the
two of them fight each other all the
time and this is what this John bini did
he made pulse frequency to make the
battery give up that energy that it
wastes prop pulsing iron can on the
inside and he gets twice as much power
out of the battery as normal
we aluminum as such as a metal it's not
something what you would say is magnetic
attractive you know it doesn't have
magnetic Blue Field to it to interact
with your magnet well we can do aluminum
and magnez we don't know what